Benjamin Vaughan Papers 1746-1900 Mss.B.V46p
American Philosophical Society
- Series II. General Correspondence, 1746-1952; 6.5 linear feet (Box 2-27)
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1812 July 24; 4 p.; Grant, Elizabeth F. Vaughan
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Vaughan, 1812 July 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 August 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 August 29; 2 p.; Rush, Benjamin, 1746-1813
  - AL to [?], 1812 August 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Parsons, Theophilus, 1750-1813, 1812 September 5; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 September 6; 3 p.; Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856
  - AL to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 September 11; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1812 September 14; 3 p.; Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856
  - ALS to Cline, Henry, 1812 September 28; 16 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1812 October 28; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1812 November 1; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - AL to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], [ca. 1812]; 5 p.; [?]
  - AL to [?], [1812]; p. 2; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner], [1812]; 4 p.; [Vaughan, H. Frances]
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1813 January 8; 1 p.; Wilde, S. S
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1813 April 6; 2 p.; Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819
  - AL to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1813 May 17; 2 p.; [?]
  - ALS to [?], 1813 May 11; 1 p.; Fawcett, Charles
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1813 May; 1 p.; Crosthwait, Leland
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1813 August 11; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - AL to [Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819], 1813 September 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Appleton, Jesse, 1772-1819, 1813 September 15; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, 1814 January 3; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Will, 1814 January 31; 5 p.; McMaster, William
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1814 May 7; 4 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - AL to [?], 1814 May 9; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Dr. Page, 9 May 1814; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1814 May 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADSty, Estate of Samuel Vaughan. Survey of water rights, 1814 November 25; 3 p.
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1814 December 28; 4 p.; Bird, H. M
  - Al to [?], [1814]; 4 p.
  - ADS, Insurance policies on shipment of goods, 1814-1822; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1815 January 3; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Sergeant, Thomas, 1782-1860, 1815 January 5; 4 p.; Page, Benjamin
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1815 January 25; 2 p.; Pickering, John, 1777-1846
  - AL to [?], 1815 Febraury 13; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Bradford, [Thomas], 1815 Febraury 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to [?], 1815 Febraury 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, 1815 February 28; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Farrer, Samuel, 1815 March 2; 1 p.; Abbott, Jacob, 1803-1879
    Purchases originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy, Oct. 1953.
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1815 March 10; 3 p.; Gardiner, Henry
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861 and Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826., 1815 March 10; 3 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - AL to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1815 March 11; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1815 April 6; 2 p.; Gardiner, Henry
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1815 April 16; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ADS, sale of a pew to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1815 June 26; 1 p.; Perley, Nathaniel
    Harlowe, Harris
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1815 June 28; 4 p.; Bird, H. M
  - ALS to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1815 August 13; 3 p.; Gardiner, Susan E
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1815 August 28, September 1; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1815 September 4; 3 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1815 September 8; 3 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1815 October 3; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Bejamin, 1751-1835, 1815 October 26; 3 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, [1815 November 29]; 3 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, 1762-1827
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1815 December 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1815 December 23; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1815 December 28; 3 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1815 December 28; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1815 December 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 January 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1816 January 21, 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - AMs, concerning hydrocephalus, 1816 January 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 January 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AL to Vaughan, John, 1756-1841, 1816 January 26; 2 p.; Letter from Benjamin Vaughan to John Vaughan, asking for books on the topic of Indian populations.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    - ALS, extract to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1815 November 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 February 3, 12; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - AL to Thacher, Rev. S. C, 1816 February 12; 16 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mrs. Darby, [1816 February 15]; 4 p.; Bird, A
  - ADS, Invoice of musical instruments shipped to William Oliver Vaughan, 1816 February 17; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 March 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1816 March 6; 1 p.; Manning, William, 1767-1849
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 March 19; 3 p.; Channing, Walter, 1786-1876
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 April 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1816 April 13, 17; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 April 19; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 April 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [?], 1816 May 6; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 June 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 June 14; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 July 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 August 20; 2 p.; Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1816 September 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1816 August 29; 1 p.; Dallas, Alexander James, 1759-1817
  - ALS to Mrs. R. H. Gardiner, [1816] December 8; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Mrs. R. H. Gardiner, 1816 December 22; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, William and Frances, [ca. 1816]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1817 January 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - AL to Vaughan, William, 1817 January; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1817 February 5, 7; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1817 February 26; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Power of Attorney, 1817 March 15; 2 p.; [McMaster, William]
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1817 March 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, J. S
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1817 March 30; 4 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1817 May 22; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1817 May 30; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1817 August 25; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1817 September 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1817 October 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Everett, Alexander Hill, 1790-1847, 1817 October 17; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1817 December 12; 1 p.; Fallman, Peleg
  - ADS, Cancelled checks, 1817-1819; 19 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 January 7; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 Febraury 11; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858], 1818 Febraury 12; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
    Purchased from Goodspeed Jan. 1952.
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 Febraury 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 March 1; 1 p.; Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 April 7; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Als to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 April 10; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 April 26; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 May 1; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 May 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 May 12; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 May 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 June 1; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - AL to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, [1818 June 2]; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 June 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 June 9; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 June 14; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 June 15; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 June 27; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 July 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 August 1; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 August 18; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Will, extracts, 1818 September 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
    - ADS, Instructions for settling Sarah Vaughan Merricks Americam properties, 1819 August 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
      housed with previous item.
  - Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1818 September 25; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - AMs, rules for making and managing cider, 1818 October 12; 8 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1818 November 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Reciepts, 1818-1819; 6 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ADS, Business papers concerning the McMaster estate, 1818-1832; 32 p.
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 January 5; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1819 January 23; 2 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner, 1819 January 29; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Mrs. Robert Hallowell Gardiner. [Emma], 1819 February 3; 4 p.; [Vaughan] Anna
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1819 February 5; 2 p.; William C. Lord and Co
  - AL to Emma Gardiner, 1819 February 20; 4 p.; [Emmons, Lucy Vaughan]
  - ALS to Emma Gardiner, 1819 February 20; 4 p.; [Grant], E Frances Vaughan
  - Als to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 February 11; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Gardiner, Robert Hallowell, 1782-1864, 1819 February 7; 4 p.; [Emmons], Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1819 February 21; 4 p.; [Emmons], Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1819 Frebruary 24; 3 p.; William C. Lord and Co
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1819 February 27; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1819 March 2; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1819 March 9; 3 p.; [Emmons], Lucy Vaughan
  - ALS Cy to Adams, [John Quincy], 1767-1848, 1819 April 3; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Hyde de Neuville, Jean Gillaume, baron, 1776-1857, 1819 April 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - Al to [?], 1819 April 10; 36 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 April 10; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 April 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 April 30; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848, 1819 May 1; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 May 11; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 May 14; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 May 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 May 20; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1819 June 12; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1819 June 23; 2 p.; Jefferson, Thomas, 1743-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1819 July 21; 2 p.; Gilmer, Francis W
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, [1819 July 28]; 1 p.; Chantrey, Francis, Sir, 1781-1841
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 August 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Power of Attorney to John Merrick and William Oliver Vaughan, 1819 August 24; 2 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 September 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 September 7; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Curry, C, 1819 September 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ADS, Bill of exchanged drawn on Samuel Perry, Jr, 1819 September 8; 1 p.; Bachelder, Nathan
    housed with previous record.
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 September 18; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1819 September 28; 2 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 October 5; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 October 22; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 October 26; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 October 27; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829, 1819 November 19; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1819 November 22; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Page, Rufus K, 1819 November 28; 1 p.; Heath, Caleb
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 February 12; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, [1820] February 20; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 March 10; 1 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - Als to Johnson & Hills, 1820 May 9; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 May 10; 2 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 May 12; 1 p.; Gitchell, John
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 May 19; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Merrick, John, 1766-1861, 1820 May 20; 3 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 May 27; 2 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ADS, Bond to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 May; 1 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 June 7; 5 p.; Page, Rufus
  - AL to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1820 June 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 June 11; 1 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 June 15; 1 p.; Snow, Gideon,
  - ALS to Warren, Eben, 1820 June 20; 1 p.; Committee of arrangements for 4th of July celebration.
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 July 3; 1 p.; Agry, Thomas Jr
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 July 7; 3 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 [July] 25; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 August 1; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 August 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 August 12; 1 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 August 29; 3 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 August 29; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to [Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835], 1820 August 31; 2 p.; Otis, Harrison Gray, 1765-1848
  - ALS to Allen, William, 1770-1843, 1820 September 8; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Allen, William, 1770-1843, 1820 September 9; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 September 24; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 September 26; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1820 September 29; 3 p.; Warren, John Collins, 1778-1856
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1820 October 9; 3 p.; Murray, Thomas
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 October 31; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1820 November 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Account with Thomas Murray, 1820 November 18; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1820 December 12; 2 p.; Page, Rufus
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 January 1; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 February 6; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 February 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Page, Rufus K, 1821 February 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1821 March 17; 3 p.; [Everett, Edward, 1794-1865]
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, [1821 March 23]; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 May 20; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADS, Permission to Jacob Abbot to remove relatives from on burial ground to another, 1821 June 4; 1 p.; Cushing, Caleb, 1800-1879
    Purchased originally with Abbott-Vaughan. Genealogy Oct. 1953.
    Pennell, Jacob; Raymond, Edward
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1821 June 7; 1 p.; Bowditch, Nathaniel, 1773-1838
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1821 June 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1821 June 8; 2 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1821 April 28; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1821 June 12; 1 p.; Davis, John, 1755-1783
  - AL to Gardiner, Emma, 1821 June 18; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1821 June 25; 1 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, Sarah Hallowell, 1824 December 18; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, Sarah Manning, 1826 May 11; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 July 8; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 July 16; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMs, Questions and answers on botanical subjects for agricultural purposes, 1821 August 1; 4 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Warren, S. S, 1821 October 11; 1 p.; Robinson, John
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 October 12; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1821 October 17; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1821 November 8; 1 p.; Vaughan, William
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1821 December; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1822 January 15, 17; 4 p.; Vaughan, Sarah
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, 1822 January 19; 3 p.; Vaughan, William Manning
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854 and Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1822 February 15; 3 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - ALS to McMaster, William, 1821 December 6; 1 p.; Allenshaw, James
  - ADS, Affidavit of the heirs of John McMaster, [1822 February]; 1 p.; Yeaton, Phineas
    Littlefield, William B.
  - Als to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1822 April 22; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1822 May 13; 2 p.; Channing, William Ellery, 1780-1842
  - Als to Dearborn, Henry, 1751-1829, 1822 May 13; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1822 May 13, 30; 6 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to [?], 1822 May 28; 4 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854; Vaughan, William
  - ALS to Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1822 May 30; 4 p.; Loveday, Arthur
  - ALS to Wells, William, 1822 May 31; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1822 May; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - ADScy, Endorsement of letter from Vaughan, Benjamin to Vaughan, William, 1822 November 20; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ADScy, statement, 1822 May 29; 1 p.; Mrs. F. W. Vaughan
  - ADScy, Receipt, 1822 May 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADScy, Release, 1826 August 30; 1 p.; Mrs. F. W. Vaughan
  - ALS Cy to Esdale, William, 1825 September 15; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ADScy, endrsement, 1825 September 24; 1 p.; Vaughan, John, 1756-1841
  - ALS to Vaughan, [Petty], 1788-1854, 1822 June 4; 2 p.; Loveday, Arthur
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1822 June 4; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Ticknor, [George], 1791-1871, 1822 August 17; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - AMsS, Poems, 1822 September 6; 34 p.; Vaughan, William Manning
  - ALS to Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835, 1822 September 20; 3 p.; Vaughan, William, 1752-1850
  - ALS to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850 and Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854, 1822 September 20; 2 p.; Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826
  - Als to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1822 October 29; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Cleavland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1822 November 3; 1 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1822 November 4; 6 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, [1822 November 29]; 2 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1822 December 28; 2 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Gardiner, Emma, [1822] December 30; 4 p.; Emmons, Lucy Vaughan
  - ADS, Catalogue of books deposited in the library of Bowdoin College, 1822 December; 20 p.; Vaughan, Samuel, Sr., 1720-1802
  - ALS to Cleaveland, Parker, 1780-1858, 1823 January 27; 3 p.; Vaughan, Benjamin, 1751-1835
  - ALS to Warren, Ebenezer, 1823 March; 2 p.; Perkins, Thomas Handasyd, 1764-1854
  - ALS to Vaughan, William Oliver, 1783-1826, 1823 April 5; 1 p.; Vaughan, Petty, 1788-1854
  - ALS Cy to Vaughan, William, 1752-1850, 1823 April 5; 1 p.; Francis and Urquhart